brianrobertcajulis@yahoo.com

# **BRIAN ROBERT CAJULIS**

#### **SUMMARY**

Graduate from Azusa Pacific University specializing in front end development for web and mobile applications. Experienced in all stages of software development process. Well practiced in various programming languages and frameworks such as JavaScript (ES6), React, React Native, MySQL, and Java.

#### **SKILLS**

Frameworks & Libraries: React, React Native, Redux, Axios,

Programming Languages: JavaScript(ES6), HTML, CSS, SASS Java, MySQL

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **ENDORSIFY - SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN**

07/2018 - 10/2018 • Los Angeles, CA

- Completed front end and back end development tasks and solve challenging interface breaking bugs
- Independently planned and developed an iOS app of their web app
- Collaborated with UX designers to create clean, user friendly interfaces
- Communicated consistently through Slack and kept progress up to date on Trello

# AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY - COMPUTER SCIENCE LAB TECHNICIAN

09/2017 - 05/2018 • Azusa, CA

- Guided students with beginner to intermediate level programming concepts
- Assisted students in Java related issues
- Communicated with students in debugging various different web and mobile projects

### AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY - CS ACTION TEAM MEMBER

05/2016 - 06/2016 • Namibia, South Africa

- Interviewed target market to create user cases to specify software features
- Participated in meetings to plan and to discuss the implementation of each feature
- Independently learned new framework and programming languages during the time frame

# **EDUCATION**

#### BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, COMPUTER SCIENCE

MAY 2018 AZUSA, CA

AZUSA PACIFIC UNIVERSITY

GPA: 3.325

# **PROJECT**

# COFFEE POT • SENIOR CAPSTONE PROJECT • 2017 - 2018

React Native, Redux, JavaScript, Firebase, Google APIs

- Coffee Pot is a mobile application used to deliver and order coffee using a peer-to-peer system
- Implemented Google Places API to fetch café places within a mile radius and sort them according to distance